Are you ready, honey?
Yes.
- Guess what, Mom.
- What?
I found out where the wasps.
Where?
Well, it has to be ...
If you throw a moth to the air,
turn it into a wasp.
- Good!
- Yes.
- How was school?
- All right.
I had a meeting with Miss. Butler.
I liked him.
Say what?
He said no entregabas your tasks.
I said, "I know that makes
the control it every night. "
He said he found several
jobs at the bottom of your backpack.
He asked me not!
Do not have to.
You just have to deliver.
And told me that you keep looking
the window throughout the day.
Not all day!
And you destroyed your sharpener.
It was not on purpose!
And several stones You stuck inside.
I thought if sharpened pencils
I could also sharpening stones.
What would you do
with sharp stones?
I wanted to make heads
arrow for my collection.
- Touch Me!
- Wait.
Mason
Samantha!
Tommy! 縈ason is there?
Yes.
- Tell him he has to come to dinner.
- OK.
- Hi.
- Hello, gorgeous.
Why are not you ready?
Hello, Mason!
Hi, Tim.
- Hurry up, come on.
- What time is it?
The nine! Come on!
I wanted to tell you that Janice
I failed. I have no babysitter.
Why do not you call another?
I can not get
one now. It is nine.
But you can stay with us.
No! We had plans.
Your friends are waiting for me.
- Well, you see.
- Okay.
Back in a couple of hours.
Is it okay?
. Yeah, it's all good.
"Back! Back!
I do not want to talk to Margo Money! "
"Who? Harry said as
hurried retreat. "
"Haunts one of the toilets
in the girls' bathroom, Hermione said. "
"Haunts a toilet?"
"Yes, it has been out of service
all year because she gets mad ...
"And inundates everything"
"Just never go there
if I can help it. "
"It's horrible trying to do
pee while she yells at you! "
Why did you say that?
- I'm sorry.
-'re Sorry. Lying.
I wanted to stay here with my children ...
Stop using children as an excuse
I know you like to stay here.
It is not necessary that ...
do not know anything!
have no responsibilities!
I the I have. Do not know
what it means to be a father.
do not know! And why I am
responsible for your mistakes in life
Errors not call my kids!
I did not say them ...!
- You said "your mistakes" ...
- I know what I said.
You use them again.
is the reality! I'm a mother!
Y means responsibility. I
love to have time to myself
I would love to go see
a fucking movie! Do not you think?
Dining out. Go to a bar.
He did not even know how!
She was the daughter of someone,
and now I'm somebody's mother!
Do you understand? I do not know how that is!
"I think I did it again,
"I played with your heart I
I lost the game. "
"Oh baby, baby
Oops! ... You thought I was in love,
"That had been sent from above,
- Enough!
- "I'm not that innocent."
Enough!
"You see my problem is this.
I'm dreaming. "
- "Wishing that heroes exist."
- Enough!
I cry, watching the days.
Am I a fool in so many ways "
What's going on?
You know what time it is?
He is ... throwing things!
Mason! Do not throw things at your sister.
Lie. She hit me first.
Listen to them both!
I'm going back to bed. I do not want to hear
no sound here for over an hour.
A sleep!
- False!
- Hey!
Look what I found on the street.
It's good, right?
Look at these!
Oops! Look at these!
Well, listen ...
I want to talk about something, and ...
might not like it
the idea at first, but ...
moved to Houston.
When?
Soon. We should do before
first to avoid paying two rents.
No, Mom, not moved.
No, no. I'm sorry, Mom. No, no.
Samantha, I need to return to the
university to improve our lives.
With my job I can not
support the family as I want.
I can not go on.
And grandma will help us.
It will be good to be around her.
Well, Mom. You can do what
anytime. But we are not moved.
What about our friends?
We will e-mail or letter.
We can go back to visit.
And guess? The place we found
Grandma will own rooms.
What's up?
And there's a pool.
Mom, do you still love daddy?
I still love your father.
But that does not mean
had been healthy to stay together.
What if, after the move,
he can not find us?
It will not be a problem.
You can call grandma.
Or call number information.
We will be easy to find.
Are you still in Alaska?
Thus says your uncle.
Taming polar bears or something.
I hope the bears tamed him.
FURNITURE MOVING AND STORAGE
- Here. Want to help?
- Clear.
Take up painting ...
carefully ...
paints and stains, marks or points ...
in the socket, behind the door ...
and the entire inner portion of the inlet.
He says he will come to visit.
I will write and call you.
Wait a second.
There is a call on the other line.
Hello?
Sorry, Tommy. Mason not
You can go today. We're moving.
I'm on the other line. Bye Bye.
縎ofia?
I'll send you instructions
for scouts.
Respond and tell me how
are the other scouts.
Because now you're the principal.
Come on. I want to get
before dark.
Goodbye garden!
Goodbye bushes! Goodbye mailbox!
Goodbye box of stuff mom
not let us go and do not want to shoot.
Goodbye house. I will never love you Mom
as before for making us move!
Samantha! Why do not you say goodbye
Also that shitty attitude?
Do not take a car ride.
Goodbye old lady listening
rock music motorbike and walk.
Hey!
What about the back?
Enough! Put separation.
Put a pillow between them.
Make a barrier. And that's enough.
We'll play something called
"The game of silence."
Which is
more quiet time wins.
You think you can do?
Come on!
The bus will arrive in ten minutes.
Put those duties in the backpack.
Eat!
Honey, go eat!
I am going!
Speak English!
Shut up!
Mom! He's talking
language that stupid again.
Samantha!
He spoke very clear English, mother.
You know it's a little slow head.
Officially flunked first grade.
- Support your butt.
- Aye, sir mother!
Well, I want you to listen.
Grandma's going to find a school.
His father came for the day.
They will spend the afternoon with him.
Will you come to live here?
I do not know.
Eight years ago have not seen him.
Moreover guy ... year and a half.
Please.
Can you eat?
The bus is coming.
Anyone want syrup?
That! Good italics.
Well, Mason. When controlling
modules, will I find yours?
- No.
- Why not?
For I have not finished.
It's time to end it.
Minute!
No, do:"Apple, quit".
Time to finish your work, Mason!
Apple, quit!
This is my history test.
Ten congratulated, great!
And this is another history test
And another "ten."
There is congratulated. Tough.
And that's my report ... lizards.
Let me see your drawings.
Right. These are my drawings.
- What's that?
- His name is Gill.
- Gill?
- Yes.
And this is the math test.
Ten again?
Mason! That was
the last candy, right?
It's okay.
When you show things ...
It is he.
OMG!
They're so big!
All right, buddy?
Do they want to have fun?
- Catherine, how are you?
- All right.
I'm glad. What time should I bring?
I'd say at 7:30.
I must take them home.
Why not take
I to him from his mother?
She expects me.
No problem.
You know get, right?
I will. No problem.
- Not a good idea.
- No problem. OK?
Are you ready?
Just a moment!
They have to carry your things.
Your backpack, your purse.
The task. Go to the bathroom.
Amazing how they have grown!
Time passes.
We should like to have them here in Houston.
I love, yes.
I volunteer at the school.
Really? What do you do there?
I'm in the library.
I read to the little ones.
What good!
So Alaska, eh?
Yes.
Are you staying?
We will see.
How is Liv?
Busy.
He returned to college.
Also working and raising two kids.
Do you have everything?
Say goodbye to grandma.
- Goodbye!
- On my way!
Just a moment ...
To you do not like
gifts, right?
- Yes!
- No, you ...
Gifts? Really? Come on!
- I'm going!
- I want to go!
Mason on the outward journey
and Samantha in the back.
Top.
- Seat belts!
- Belts. Sure!
Do not forget the belts.
Neither has this car seat.
All right. All right. All right!
Very well!
Come over! Yes!
It was awesome!
Now you, Mason, touches you!
It was very good!
Come on!
Show them who
are you, friend. I show him.
Yes! Yes!
Yes!
It's okay. Do not worry.
I wish I'd packed.
The stops are for children.
Do you have two years?
They serve the stops.
Life does not give you caps.
There he goes! Now!
Anything goes!
The last time I had packed.
It was much more fun.
They serve the stops.
Yes all playing with low
stops, it means nothing.
Believe me.
Lane only deposit it well.
One ... two ... three, ...
Viva el father!
Four Blackwater employees were
savagely attacked in Fallujah.
The rebels set fire
the bodies and cars, and ...
See? It is a disaster.
I will tell you what is happening in Iraq.
Exactly what every person
thinking I knew it would happen.
A Bush and fans who
around them a damn.
25 cents!
What?
You said "fuck".
Forgiveness.
My teacher says it is a just war
because prevention is better than cure.
Is that what they teach you?
Listen to your father.
It's a lie. It is the big lie.
Iraq had nothing to do with what the
twin towers. I know, right?
I suppose.
By whom will vote, MJ?
- I dunno.
- You can not vote. There is 18 years old.
Who did you vote for?
- Perry?
- Anyone but Bush! OK?
Will you come back to live here?
It's what I want.
I need to find work.
Will you ever hang out with mom?
I do not know. No ... just depends on me.
I remember when I was six.
You and Mom fought like crazy.
You scream so loud and mother cried.
Is that what you remember?
Yes.
Do not you remember Galveston travel?
And when we camped in
Big Bend and had fun?
No.
- Do you ever get mad at your mother?
- Yes.
- What about your brother?
- Yes!
- Do they have you cried?
- Yes, of course.
But that does not mean
not want, right?
The same happens when you're an adult.
You get angry with people.
It's nothing important.
What did you do in Alaska?
I worked on a boat ... for a while ...
I tried to compose music.
Did you see a polar bear?
No, but I saw a Kodiak bear.
The fucking was huge!
Dad! They are 50 cents
for using that word!
Forgiveness.
Take a dollar. Keep the change.
I will be seeing more often now.
I missed a lot. I want them to know.
I needed time for myself.
Your mom and I ...
His mother ... is ... difficult.
I think they know.
And I'm ... I'm happy
be with you two.
And sorry about the issue of the stops.
I think I'm better than that. Is it okay?
This I found in Dripping Springs
Roddy and ... my friend gave me this.
- And I bought it.
- Did you buy it?
- Did you find her in Dripping Springs?
- Yep.
Hottie! What else you got?
These are vertebrae of snakes.
縑ertebrae of snakes? Yuck!
Mason, I do not want you to gather
more vertebrae of snakes.
- This is the pen that I sent you?
- Yes.
Dad! I forgot to show you
these photos ... basketball.
- Are you on a basketball team?
- Yes.
What good!
- Look at the claws of beavers.
- Claws of beavers?
縌uests beavers?
What position do you play?
Base.
This is dissected Canadian grass.
- You score?
- 8 to 10 per game.
? to 10? Incredible!
Once he scored no points and wept.
- Did you cry?
- A little.
Hi!
Mason! Came mom!
- Came mom!
- Reached mom.
Mom! Hi!
See the owl I
He gave Dad. Is not it good?
The head spins. Look at the bracelet.
Made by Indians in Alaska.
Dad gave me this bear
carved by hand and this tiki.
It is a totem.
And guess! We played bowling
and had four perfect shots!
And we could ride in Dad's car.
- Hey, Liv.
- Hi.
I know you wanted
let them hear about your mother.
I thought it would be easier here.
You ruined my plans.
- We wanted to show the rooms.
- Yes.
Did you eat anything?
Ate fries
at the bowling alley.
- Did you do your homework?
- No. - Not yet.
Can I talk to you outside for a second?
Yes, of course.
They ate more fries.
Do you think he will stay for the night?
Apparently not.
An unconditioned stimulus,
something that produces ...
unlearned response,
involuntary and not conditioned.
What was the stimulus used
by Pavlov in his experiment?
Come on! Was it hard to
week? What? Meat!
Meat. Or rather, meat powder.
Whatever it was dust
meat, it worked with your dog.
He placed the meat powder and produced
unconditioned response ...
the dog was salivating ...!
OK?
Who can give me another example of a
unconditioned response to the stimulus ...
happens every day.
Perhaps it is occurring
any of you now.
What about sex?
Come to an attractive member
the opposite sex and have a ...
automatic response.
Not even have to think about it.
Mick Jagger wrote a song:
"Oh, when you named salivate
like a Pavlov dog. "
Thank you very much. End of class.
Dr. Welbrock.
This is my son, Mason.
Mason, this is Dr. Welbrock.
Your son! I thought it was a genius
Children who attended my class.
He was not feeling well, so I brought.
No fever. It is a hoax.
I know because my son
nine years he always does.
The same matter.
- Do you play football?
- No.
My son either. He hates football.
He likes computers.
My daughter loves it 11
football. Who understands it?
Maybe we could join us sometime.
Maybe, yes.
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
- Nice, Mason.
- Nice.
And thanks for coming to my class.
Olivia.
- Cute kid.
- Thank you!
Do you think Grandma will
available to care for the kids?
Perhaps.
- Really?
- Yes.
To awaken the dead!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, you're alive!
Touch Me!
Guys! They arrived!
Quick, quick!
WELCOME NEWLYWEDS
We're back!
- I missed you!
- Hey, Dad!
Samantha, Mason, thank you!
Samantha and I did it alone.
I know that men do not go that high.
A distribute gifts!
We take a huge lift. Top
all throw a paper airplane.
What happened?
It flew!
He flew several kilometers.
Will they kissed under
Bridge of Sighs?
- Yes.
- We did.
- Mom, can we see your ring?
- Clear.
It is a stepped ring,
surrounded by bright miniature.
- I wish we could go to Europe.
- Yes.
We go as a family next time.
Not much is lost.
We were at the hotel ...
playing video games.
Really?
And the hotels are
very young and very old.
Did I get you anything else?
You want the dessert menu?
I said lay it up.
Keep it in your wallet, please.
Little games on the table.
Another bottle of wine, please.
A coke.
Mason, you're okay with water.
Just coca. Thank you.
And what about you?
Did you finish your science project?
Not yet.
Did you work? 縔ou built
something or something you planned?
- A little.
- Did you do anything, Mindy?
No.
Have you sat with Mason
and little games all the time?
Yes.
You had to finish
that before my return.
Do you remember?
- Grevious is the best.
- Yoda! Yoda!
- Has four arms!
- Yoda!
Miss Odio. Burnsley.
Everyone thinks it's a lesbian.
It is. It is suggested to Stacy.
- Yuck!
- Is it true?
Always walk around the locker room.
I think I saw a couple of ...
Paul! Tell us a joke.
Fuck! Fuck!
Fuck you! Ass!
- I gave you!
- That was not fair.
Yes it was. It was more just world.
Yes! Again I got.
Does the mask?
Do the three musketeers?
First word.
- Chicken?
- Chicken.
Second word.
- Hoodie.
- Big Hair ... Robin Hood!
Second word.
縈anta?
Props, no!
Talk a judge. No on props.
You can not use props.
You can do without that. Think!
Moving ... Witnesses?
Folding ...
Something with a blanket.
- Crack ...
- A crack in time!
Harry Potter
and the Deathly Sale
Are you ready?
Count together, ladies
and gentlemen:10 ... 9 ... 8 ... 7 ...
6 ... 5 ... 4 ... 3 ... 2 ... 1 ...
Come on!
No, no, no. Back
and practice the first blow.
Gently.
Sweep the floor, sweep the floor.
As well.
Do not hit hard.
Always hits it too hard.
Very well!
Your feet farther back.
As well. Now you can hit straighter.
Hit. A soft knock
and slow will be the best for you.
Very well!
You have ... Your feet
are too open, Randy!
Naturally.
Yes! Very well!
High five.
Good putt, son, good putt.
Did you see that, Randy? This is done.
Putt for birdie!
Fuck!
Son of a bitch!
Will you bring me sticks? Go get the ball.
For if we have visitors this weekend.
He always says that,
but never have visitors.
Samantha, I think you got your dad.
All right.
Did they finish the housework?
Not all.
Almost.
縔ou took the powder, Sam?
Not yet.
I saw you with your art project.
Did you have time to finish
but not for your chores?
I thought we had talked.
I can remove dust.
No. You have your own
tasks and Sam has his.
It's simple!
Bad decision, Sam.
Mason!
He arrived your dad.
No blinding for speed, right?
How did? Does half? Eh!
- They finished?
- No.
縏ask completed?
What will you do tomorrow?
- The same, right?
- Yes.
Come in.
Goodbye, Mom.
Goodbye dear. I love you.
- Goodbye, Mom.
- Goodbye, little girl.
- Have fun with your father.
- Wait, Mason.
The boys did not end with the leaves.
Samantha did not end with the dust ...
So tomorrow, when they return,
instead of swimming or other
things they like to do,
- They will finish their homework, okay?
- Yes.
Well, I have spoken. Do you understand?
Thank you. Sought your support
not to be the only one who yells.
I support. Get it?
Does everyone agree? Tomorrow, tasks ...
I do not hear. Les enters
by one ear and out the other.
Dad does not make sense to remove dust.
Yes it does.
It's just that you do not like it.
Who spends the duster today?
You when we tell you!
Olivia, do not let me answer
and in front of the other. Thank you.
Samantha, please ...
What ever.
Bye Bye. The pass very well.
Bye, guys. I love you.
Sorry but what we talked about. There are
to draw a line and get tough.
Yes, it is ...
have many lines, Bill.
Everything is online.
Hi, Randy! Hi, guys.
And how are you two?
I'm going forward.
- I post this. Are you okay, honey?
- Yes.
- And you, champ?
- I'm fine.
What good!
On my way!
Are you ready for the big game?
- Yes.
- Against whom the Astros playing today?
I do not know.
Brewers Milwaukee.
Know them, hate them.
Mason, what about you?
How was your week?
Pretty good.
What did you do?
- Nothing.
- You keep hanging out with Joe?
- Yep.
- Is your best friend yet?
I think so.
- And you? How was your week?
- All right.
What did you do?
Nothing important.
Still ... working with sculpture?
Yes. Almost finished.
What is it?
You're welcome.
No, no, no, no.
So we will not talk with us.
I will not be that guy.
They can not put me in that category.
The "biological father
who I am every 15 days ...
"I chat with who kindly ...
"As he takes me aside
to another and buys me things. "No!
Talk to me!
"Samantha, how was your week?"
"It was hard. Separated Billy and Ellen ...
"Ellen is angry because
he saw me talking to Billy ...
"In the dining room. Remember the
sculpture he was doing?
"It was a unicorn horn
broke. Now it's a zebra. "
"But I think it'll take me like 10"
"Mason, how was your week?
"You know, it was pretty hard.
"Joey is dumb medium.
"He stole cigarettes
mother and wanted me to smoke.
"I said no because I knew what
that will cost you leave, Dad. "
What's up? Is it so difficult?
These questions are
difficult to answer.
What is so difficult
describe a sculpture?
It's Abstract!
OK. OK, fine.
Ni did not even know ...
you were interested in abstract art.
I'm not interested. I oblige.
But, dad, why
always us? What about you?
How was your week?
Who do you walk? You have a girlfriend?
What have you done?
You're right.
So we have to leave
everything comes naturally, right?
That's what you say.
OK! It's what we do.
From now.
Look at this!
It is a ...
It is an owl butterfly.
Caligo Atreus.
Look at this!
What kind is it?
Looks like a zebra long-winged.
- Very well!
- Good.
This is amazing.
- That is the Owl, right?
- Yes
Owl butterfly.
I peed, friend.
1 ... 2 ... 3 ... 4 ...
five.
Get away from me!
Mason! Look at me.
Form a diamond with your hands.
Fingers and thumbs. Soft hands.
Sam.
Very well.
This is done.
Still running, you still
thinking of the diamond.
Diamond, and soft hands.
Right.
Come on, Roger!
They can not stick when he throws balls.
So they know what they are watching.
It is history. You see this guy?
Its 43 years
and leaves rates hit 20.
He has a batting average of 1.47.
What can you believe?
If the Astros could make some
bases, we would win a game.
Dad, do you have a job?
Why do you ask that?
Mom wanted to know ...
Mom wanted to know.
Tell Mom ...
they just happen ... I just
my second actuarial exam.
And then ...
How is she?
- Finishing college?
- Yes All 10..
Do all 10 eh?
The mother went to the daughter, right?
- Hey, Jimmy.
- Hi, Samantha.
- What about Jimmy?
- What about Mason?
Astros won.
Were the party?
Am I the only one with arms?
No one else can bring anything?
And help your man?
What are you looking at?
Jimmy, you know who came
guys this weekend.
For once,
Could not you help me a little?
- Sorry, Muffin.
- Do not give me Muffin.
I'm not the fucking dog Tony Randall.
- Dad is always messy.
- It was not the morning.
- I cut the grass.
- Good.
Come on, get that shit.
Give me that.
- Did you see the match?
- No.
Lane won a
career three-pointers.
It was beautiful, right?
Sam went crazy.
He is a fan of the Astros.
You sure.
Lunar eclipse on Saturday night
sang a song, something like:
my tired children sleep
sirens pass
Tonight we
safe here in Houston
with this lullaby Dad
Her mother has a new husband now
seems all well
I wonder if they storytelling
and if you give them a kiss good night
They say they miss me
should not wish that were true
The teacher says my child
draws pictures of a family
all blue.
He says he was surprised
whispering to the window:
"Daddy, please come home"
I know I could call
but what if the mother takes the call
- Did you brush your teeth?
- What?
Did you brush your teeth?
Yes.
Are not you stay asleep
with these bullrings posts?
Perhaps.
Try not.
- I turn off the light?
- Yes.
- Good night, Sam.
- Good night, Dad.
- Goodnight, Jimmy.
- Today was fun, right?
- Yes, it was. I'm sorry.
- What?
- That has to be Mason.
- Good night.
Dad?
In reality there is ...
magic in the world, right?
What do you mean?
You know, like ... elves and stuff.
People invents.
I dunno.
What makes you think that
magical elves are something like ...
like a whale.
Do you understand me?
What if I tell you how ...
under the ocean there is this ...
giant mammal using
sonar and sing songs?
And what's so great that his heart
is the size of a car, and could ...
crawl through your arteries?
You seem quite magical, right?
Yes.
But ... say ...
at this very moment,
no elves in the world, right?
No. In short, no elves.
Be well, guys.
Have a great week.
- Sam, see you this weekend.
- Yes. Right, I forgot.
Cindy's birthday on Saturday.
- You're sleeping?
- Yes.
I'll talk to your mom.
Do not worry. Have a good time.
How do you not know how to do this?
I will soon markers.
Randy Mason, Dad wants down.
- For what?
- Haircuts.
It will look much better.
You look like a man and not a little girl.
And eyebrows too, right Byron?
Mason, we're leaving.
You're not sick!
- Bye, guys.
- Goodbye, Mom.
And Mason?
It does not feel good.
I will not go to school.
The patient does.
Ya.
Mason, what happens?
I do not feel well.
Your head is fine,
so out of bed.
I'm taking.
You have five minutes. Do not be late.
Neither asked me!
He cut and ready.
Is my hair!
No wonder you're angry.
I would be too.
I am a Martian now.
Honey, I'll talk to him
later, okay?
You should have called
but he had the phone.
I'm sorry.
I've been so
busy with college ...
If it helps, it's just hair
and will grow again.
Now I can see your
nice eyes and your face fox.
And why did you marry
with him? It is a total moron.
Bill has its good things.
Nobody is perfect.
And now we have a family.
We already had a family.
"I pledge allegiance to the flag of
United States of America,
"And to the republic
by which it is held,
"One nation under God, indivisible,
"With liberty and justice for all."
Recite the oath of Texas.
"Honor the Texas flag;
"I pledge allegiance, Texas,
"One state under God,
one and indivisible. "
Thank you. Have a seat.
Ya!
As you know, we are
working with mythology,
and will write about gods and goddesses.
We have listed
Gods on the board.
There are a couple
monsters for those interested.
They will write an essay
about gods and goddesses.
To address all issues,
make sure you do all these things.
First, we must
name the god or goddess.
And you have to add the "who", "what" ...
MASON, YOUR HAIR I LOVE IT!
"When", "where", "why" and "how".
Verify that it is
all to write the essay.
Donkey.
- See you.
- Yes.
- Mom, are you okay?
- What happened?
No, no. Go to the house.
A house. Go to the house!
Your mother had an accident.
And now it's melodramatic
Get off the fucking
floor, Olivia. God.
I'll take a drink with my dinner.
Anyone else have a problem with that?
- Samantha?
- No.
- Mindy?
I thought not.
I do not like me very much, do you, Mason?
I did not like me very much.
Do you think that's funny?
You think that's funny?
What's wrong? Do you feel left out?
Clean it, shit! Clean it up!
Clean it motherfuckers! I hate pumpkin!
Girl, I'll pay. I have three
jobs right now ...
How many times you'll see it, Mason?
It is funny.
I'm with my friend now.
Reviewing my C.V.
I'll stick
You know what? You need to calm down.
I want my money!
Why do you need fast
Had already been so wrong?
No, but I cried a lot.
But throwing and breaking things.
Yes. You are drunk. I knew it.
You're drunk.
Their cell.
So nobody talked to her.
- Mason?
- No.
- Mindy?
I believe you.
- Samantha?
- No.
I did not talk to her. He left a message.
What did it say?
Not much.
Would return later.
Is that all?
"Do I'll be back later," click?
He said, "Stay in
Quarter back later. "
Answer it be
in their rooms. Nothing more.
Yes.
Where is?
- I do not know.
- Where is he?
Said No!
All the car.
Fast! The car!
REMOVE YOUR RECEIPT
INSUFFICIENT FUNDS
- Still not working.
- Shit.
It took everything.
Randy, go to collect it.
Tell him I'm not feeling well or something.
Mason, accompany it!
Take my identification.
Good evening, folks.
How I can help?
What's this?
This is not you!
Who is?
It is our ... father.
It does not feel good.
Yes! I know.
Let's see.
Five hundred dollars.
Do not forget to identification.
Take care of your father, son. You only have one.
Fuck!
Out of the way! God!
Samantha!
Mason!
Where the fuck have you been?
I leave you, Bill. We're out of here.
I doubt it.
Samantha, Mason! Lower!
I do not think.
- And this one?
- I'm not here for you!
I know. You are here to protect
my wife. Thank you.
Back!
Why do not you come?
Sign. What the devil are you doing?
Get back up. They will not go anywhere.
Enough! Come on!
Where do they think they are?
- No one's going anywhere, dammit.
- Enough!
- No, fucking ...
- Do not touch my children!
- Okay. Take them.
- Do not touch!
- Get in the car!
- Take them! Take them!
Adelante!
Get in!
Olivia!
Place yourselves belts.
Where are we going?
We'll stay in Carol a while.
Do not look back!
Everything will be fine.
Lee and Mason. Take
a break. Here's sandwiches.
Hey, Abby.
Can I get help?
Why not come Randy and Mindy?
I'm not his legal guardian, my love.
It would be a kidnapping. I can not ...
What will happen?
What happens when the tutor
is dangerous and abusive legal?
I do not know, honey.
I called his mom. I called
the protection agencies.
Here I have you and your brother.
We are in a situation
dangerous. It is my responsibility.
Will be back to see?
I do not know.
I hope so.
How long we will be here?
Not much. We are ...
I have no answers for everything!
Hey. We are happy to
long as they want them.
The time needed.
It's fun, right?
Like having an older sister.
Like having a brother.
We will help at all.
Neither will notice our presence.
Mom, is horrible!
You leave me in the parking lot
school. Do not know anyone.
I left all my friends
and I could not even say goodbye.
Do not know where to go!
Samantha, simply
to pass that door.
The office is there.
Await you. They will give you your schedule.
Here you go for lunch.
I'll find you here at 3 and 30.
I'm with dirty clothes, because ...
Not let us go
find our stuff!
Neither have a place to live!
It stinks!
Samantha!
I do the best I can!
And you're right, it sucks!
But not stink half as
what an idiot drunk sucks ...
banging your head against the wall!
So enough with the attitude
shit! Strap yourself.
If you need anything I'll be in the classroom 112.
This is the classroom of Mrs.. Darby.
Everything will be fine, honey.
Mom!
YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR
YOUR OWN ACTIONS!
Are you Mason?
I am Mrs. Darby.
Nice to meet you.
Sit here.
- Kenny.
- Yes, ma'am.
Kenny, this is Mason
and I want you to show the place today.
Hello. Welcome to the mess.
The class! Listen!
We have a new student with us.
His name is Mason.
It is sitting in the back row.
Kenny will be your buddy, but ...
want everyone to take
time to show up today
and welcome to the school.
Is it okay? Begin.
What do you want?
Can we put a
Obama poster in your garden?
Do I look to support
Barack Hussein Obama?
No.
It is private property, leave.
You could shoot!
- What an idiot.
- Had a southern flag at home.
I love it. Young people
work supporting Obama. What good!
Did you make it through school?
Our dad is a big fan.
What good. We have to
together to win.
Yes.
I want both!
I had a dream in which she kissed.
He is so handsome, right?
I made some shirts for
my children, "My Mama supports Obama."
- Do you like it? - Yes.
- It's good, right?
Thanks for the poster!
Very well! Looking good!
How many were you? Two?
Let's go. Come on, Sam.
- Go for the poster McCain.
- What?
McCain poster.
Crank it! Come on.
Bring it! Yes, yes, yes!
Good job.
I'm proud of you.
They are going to arrest you for you.
I am a patriot.
Sometimes you have to fight in life.
And what do you do at these parties?
I do not know ... I talk, dance, listen to music.
And what's more fun than going
I camp with your brother and your father?
Yes.
Sorry!
Will there be alcohol?
I think not. Perhaps some
of the bigger guys.
I know what the party is about.
The parents are out
someone got a keg of beer,
will be great fun;
They will destroy the entire house.
- No?
- No, Dad. Amy is very responsible.
Who will be there?
Maureen, Christine, Amy ... everyone!
Will the guy
on your Facebook page?
Who?
That is hugging you
and has hair over his eyes.
- Garrett?
- Garrett? So it called?
Will Garrett there?
- It is probable.
- Probable...
I learn more from her
on his Facebook page ...
that his sparkling conversation.
Is he your boyfriend?
Something like that.
Do you know him? Have you been in the house?
Sometimes.
縑ece "s"?
Do you have a boyfriend!
- Ever heard of Sarah Palin?
- Yes.
What that insurance
you know your 17 year old daughter?
- What are pregnant?
- That's right.
And what is it that you will not be sure ...
within two years, turned 17?
- Pregnant?
- Exactly.
What are the two
ways to achieve that goal?
The first ... not having
relationships, OK? That's the first.
Do not be ... That did not work
well for your mother and me.
And what is the second?
- Where you going?
- To the bathroom.
No need to go to the bathroom.
Sit, Mason.
What is the second form?
Her mother has not spoken to them about this?
- Dad. - No, seriously.
Do you have talked about ...
contraceptives?
What? Do you have ...?
Condoms, have you spoken to them about it?
- Dad, please.
- What?
- Stop it, please.
- Garrett has ...?
- God!
- What?
Sam, we need to talk about this.
Come on, we can.
Just hear me out, okay?
It's so hard for me and for you.
Seriously, I read an article
in a newspaper the other day,
saying that although adolescents
USA were not sexually active
have equal rate
highest pregnancy.
Hello.
- Tammy, how are you?
- Good to see you.
Yeah, me too.
Tammy, this is my daughter Samantha.
And this son is Mason.
- Saluda.
- Hi.
Hello, Mason. Encantada.
I've heard of you.
- What are you doing here?
- I'm with friends.
And what are you doing?
We will camp.
Although she will not go
camp. You go to a party.
- Funny.
- We men, camp.
Males camp. Very well.
Is on for tomorrow?
Yeah. Leave at 7 and I'll call you.
All right. It was a pleasure
meet you both. Bye Bye.
- Bye Bye.
- See you.
Do not look like that.
Well, to end it.
I was 23 when you were born.
Y Tu Mama Tambien.
We did not put in the best
situation to be great parents.
And I would be a better parent ...
for you two, you know?
And I hope you can
learn from my mistakes.
That is, use a condom.
Or ... Garrett ... whatever.
Listen to this song.
I wanted to be busy
Traditional song lyrics and "country"
Traditional old school.
I wash the dishes, short grass
Listen to the quality of production.
It's like ... "Abbey Road"
tried to keep busy
Although I know you'll never
You know, the woman left. Traditional.
Uncool.
I try to keep the house tidy
I make my bed, change the sheets
Until I learned to use the washing machine
Having everything clean does not change anything
I think I have your expertise.
Will you seek teaching jobs?
I think what he has done.
Yeah? Where?
- Everywhere.
- Why all of Texas?
- Yes -. If you have to move
you have to move. It's no big deal.
We'll handle it.
I'll keep going every two weeks.
If you move at 800 km or so
drive must be longer.
It is not a problem.
- I'm sick of moving.
- Sure.
But you never know.
Maybe I have to move.
I am working to
an insurance company.
These companies are
bought and sold all the time.
We will have to accept it.
I thought you were a musician.
I am, but ... Life is expensive, you know.
You have to be responsible.
What do you think?
Hey, you! What a lack of respect!
And the redhead in the bowling alley?
Yeah, what's up?
- You know her well?
- We've seen a few times.
Is your girlfriend?
What do you mean?
Well ... you've kissed?
Yes. Yeah, I've kissed.
And you? You have a girlfriend?
Something like that.
Really?
Did you ... kissed?
No.
What have they done?
- Talk on the phone.
- Clear.
- How about that?
- Pretty bad.
Why?
At school we can
talk about many things, but ...
the phone seems to
we have nothing in common.
Nothing?
Not interested in music
and electronic games ...
The three best films of the summer.
The Dark Knight, A War
Film and Pineapple Express
- So?
- It says that all stink!
What interests you?
I dunno. Go downtown
shopping with their girlfriends silly.
- Is she pretty? Careful there.
- Yes.
Do the following.
First, you're doing a lot of questions.
And then you have to listen to
responses. Demonstrate interest in her.
If you can do that you will
light years ahead of the others.
It is the best merengue
soft roast my life.
It is awesome. I look at it.
Light brown, without burns ...
What could be sold in a store.
Worth a commercial.
- Worthy of an ad.
- Yes.
Do you think it will take another
Star Wars?
I dunno. If they made another ...
should be in the game period.
- Then there is nothing.
- Yes.
- Return of the Jedi was finished.
- There's nothing else to do.
You can transform
Hans Only a Sith lord.
If I could leave this motorway
Without me killed or caught
I will walk on that road
in a cloud of smoke
to a land
ever, I have never bought
- Good day.
- Good.
- Do you have to pee?
- Yes.
Aim the fire.
Custom ... old native.
Give the earth what it took.
And while not the forest fire risk.
Good. Have a good time.
Mason, do not forget. I have a class
later today. Sam will you find.
- Yes, Sam?
- Yes.
- Bye Bye!
- See you.
Hello.
Is that all you got?
Good luck with that.
- Do not push me! Putita.
- I did not.
Are you saying I'm lying?
No.
Do not be evil, motherfucker.
It seems that the baby
Cute is not very good.
Do not touch me, fagot!
You're an asshole.
Hello, Mason!
Hi, Jill.
Where are you going?
To university.
What happens there?
- My mom taught.
- Good.
- What does it teach?
- Psychology, I think.
What do you do?
My mom owns Neilworks.
Are the artists and artisans.
So I'm walking around.
I have to go to the hospital soon.
Why?
Do you know Courtney?
The girl with dyed hair
black and a nose ring?
Use halter neck ever ...
I think so.
We were best friends,
but we have drifted apart.
He became very emo,
I believe very snobbish, but ...
still consider you my friend.
Well, she cut one of his wrists.
I do not know the seriousness,
but I think I should visit.
What are you reading?
"Breakfast of Champions"
Kurt Vonnegut.
I think he likes my big brother.
I'm reading
"To Kill a Mockingbird" for the third time.
My friends tease me.
I must be the only girl in school
did not read the Twilight books.
- Do you read?
- Of course not.
I tried ... but it was so cheesy!
How about San Marcos?
It's okay.
It is much smaller
Houston, but not bad.
- Have you always lived here?
- Yes.
If you want a big city here,
you have to go to San Antonio or Austin.
Do you know?
I went to San Antonio
for the day, but not Austin.
It's where the big kids go.
Weekends, for concerts and stuff.
So I've been told.
Are you going to the party
Shawna next weekend?
Something I heard, but I'm not sure.
- You should.
- Why?
Nana's crazy about you
and I know he wants you.
Do not have a girlfriend, right?
Not at the time.
Well, you must come.
- I'll call first for
sure you are. - OK.
Do not tell Nana
I said that. It would kill me.
I will not.
- I have to go. See you.
- Bye Bye.
Their cognitive series.
His interviews with orphans.
His work ethology.
And then he, in turn,
was supported by ...
study
Rhesus macaques Harry Harlow.
Think it was the decade
1950 It was something radical!
This contradicted
to the classical theory of learning ...
conditioning
B.F. classic Skinner.
Bowlby argued that ...
human survival
depends on us fall in love.
Depends on who I love with my mom.
And my mother was in love with me.
And if it does not,
we are doomed.
Think about it. A tiger runs
our tribe through the cave.
An ideal mother
"My baby! I love you!'ll Protect you!"
Or "You? For what I'll
to help? I entorpecer醩 you. "
"You ... tiger food."
Next week we'll talk
of the four stages of Bowlby's attachment.
Some of you
have class with Elena.
She and I will host
a meeting at my house.
Whoever wants to come, welcome.
I'm not a great cook.
Samantha!
Why the hell
You were not your brother?
I know what you're gonna say ...
She was late
and we could not turn around.
No excuses! Specifically no
did what you said you would do.
You left your brother!
I am ashamed
ask my friend to turn around and ...
go find a child of eight.
How does a child? He's your brother!
You know, we would ask before Janie.
The school is
around the corner, it's no problem.
Forgiveness.
You have to start
thinking about who you want to be.
Want to be a person
cooperating and has compassion,
that helps people?
Or do you want to be a callous egomaniac?
You're right. I am a person
horrible, but he's not a baby anymore.
And you should treat it as such.
It is in the eighth grade and ...
You can only get home if you like.
You know what? When Gabby
you can go and have a talk.
- Cornered!
- That sucks.
- What about?
- Camp tonight.
- Are you coming?
- Who is going?
My brother, one of
Tony and his friends ... maybe.
I ask my mother.
Mom, I can go camping with Chase today?
Where?
The home being built
his family. It is almost finished.
Will there be ... adult?
Your brother is older.
- Do you have your phone?
- Yes.
Burdened?
Get the telephone number
and direction of their parents on the counter.
That! Way to go!
Not bad. But this will be supreme.
Let's see what
I can do. This is your face.
Break his face here.
Okay, now look at this.
Better get moving.
Look at this.
This stuff is lethal.
It would be very painful.
A beer. It was very good.
Brewing time.
No thanks.
Bring it on.
Are you a fag?
I do not like drinking beer.
If you cringe a beer,
sure you ever fucked a girl.
- You okay?
- Clear.
When?
- In the summer.
- Who?
Chase and made easy
grabbed Nancy Hooker.
- Thus says.
- It was. Would I lie?
Do not make up. Quick, where were you?
At Tober.
She was with a couple of other types.
His debut was with a used!
And you, Mason? Have you already taken?
Already hit him cry that night?
- Sometimes.
- Really?
You sure. How was it?
Manuela ?
No ... Jennifer.
Not here. It was in Houston.
Lie!
I do not care if you do not believe me.
In other words, in Houston you were the big male ...
but to get here ... left foot!
Fuck you! I would,
but the girls here do not want.
It's not what they want!
It's what you want.
Truth.
You know what?
Join a band and go.
- Yes?
- Of course!
You do not even have to play well.
You start to play your instrument
and the girls line up to suck your dick.
But not you.
The ladies do not care so much ...
who plays the flute in the band.
I'm not in the marching band!
Are you sure?
I heard you played the flute of meat!
I ask a question.
If they are so great, why are
three idiots on a Friday night?
Shut up, Forrito.
You're lucky to be here.
It is our camp.
The only reason
why you are here ...
is the mother of Charlie
forced to bring the setting of his brother,
and he brought you
two fucking assholes.
Fucking assholes!
All right.
These children will
his chance soon.
Later whores come.
- Yes?
- That's it!
I know Chase is caught anything.
I've seen clutching the walls.
What about you two? Can score?
What ever.
And you, great blower?
I dunno. Perhaps.
All good if you're gay.
Understand. But sleeping there.
I'm not gay.
Give it time. Now you will notice.
Fuck you!
That's what I said!
There are whores. The we were
fucking to see what they said.
Achieve a badge.
Put it next to your card bitch.
Because you're a whore. Take this.
- As little whore.
- Putita!
This is called the stroke of death.
Came! What good.
Here, hostess.
Thank you. Something to eat?
- Good.
- Thank you.
- You did?
- Yes.
- How long do you work?
- Not much.
After the summer camp.
Is there a camp for graffiti?
They call it street art.
To look less illegal, but ...
actually serves to
get free spray paint.
Great.
This is your label?
So ... just call it ...?
Yes, but they are only letters,
what I can do.
E ... C ... K, J, O.
"Kecjo".
Great.
It means nothing.
- Is your dad?
- Yes.
- Where do you live?
- In Houston.
Do you see him often?
Some weekends and in the summer.
You are a student of my mom, right?
Yes, it's me ... I have a class with her.
It is good.
How do you do? Are you a good teacher?
Very good! Very clever
and ... he cares about things.
Makes class interesting.
Probably my favorite teacher.
We found a way to amplify
our iPods in the car.
When we reached a village,
knew that the 456 was there ...
because we were jumping,
jump here, jump there.
Out the entire family.
Were the kids and ...
mother and father and jumped all.
We threw candy to the kids,
soccer balls, dolls and frisbees.
Cigarettes for adults and ...
really loved the Gatorade.
But for some reason,
hated the lemon-lime flavor.
I do not know what happened.
Or given away.
How long were you there?
Two periods of service
in Iraq and one in Bosnia.
縔ou enlist?
Yes, I was in the Guard
National barely finished high school.
Needed money to
college and paid well.
I did my tour of duty.
At the end, I said, 'I will return if
something happens to change the world. "
Three months later
what happened to the twin towers and back.
And I'm proud that throughout the
time I was there with the 456,
never lost anyone, not one.
That's weird, unusual?
Yes.
Almost impossible.
Those who came to replace us ...
They did not hear our
advice. They did everything backwards.
And they lost
seven soldiers in the first month.
What that
you did differently?
I like to think is
a matter of mutual respect.
All the time
dedicated to establishing trust,
they destroyed it in three days.
According to the natives,
Why are we there?
Oil. Plain and simple.
Mason!
Arrived.
Hey! Kids Club!
Already out of the car.
Crawl out the window
back or whatever.
I'll miss you.
See you Sunday night.
Send me text messages.
Do you have any gum?
Yes. Here.
Thank you. See you.
Accept the account
Party to be ...
guilt and redemption
their own retirement, as if ...
whatever that corrupts this country.
Hello, Mason. What time is it?
Type ... 12 and 15.
Happy Birthday.
Happy Birthday!
Mason! Is it your birthday?
Right now, it seems.
- How old are you?
- 15.
A hug!
Happy Birthday. Wow!
Have you drunk?
And you?
A little. And you?
A little bit.
Do you also have ...?
I'm going to sleep.
We talk in the morning, okay?
Dad!
How are you?
- Who owns the car?
- It's ours.
Hop.
- Hello!
- Hey, baby.
Hello, Cooper!
How's it going?
Hello, brother. It's so cute.
Can not we replace
that part of the pipe?
No, not work. Everything is in disrepair.
- Everything all?
- Yes, everything. Mira.
This is ...
- Stronger?
- It's better. Yeah yeah.
Thanks for the camera
that you gave to Mason.
- A Mason likes photography.
- Yes.
He says he wants to transform
her closet in a dark room.
Red light and revealed. Everything.
- Do not you have problem?
- I will not see him for a week.
He's having fun.
At least he is focused on something.
I like that.
This on its own.
OK, on ??to the "large".
It's good. It is better, yes.
You're smart, you should be studying.
I like the study,
I need it, but ...
It's hard. I work all day ...
Go to night school! Education
Community tertiary. It is not expensive.
Good job with the house. Looks great.
- Thank you.
- Very well.
We fix here and there.
We got it cheap at auction.
Now I know why.
- Happy Birthday!
- What about that?
It's our new car!
Come up.
Have a good weekend.
- Hello!
- How you doing?
- Good to see you.
- Me too.
How are you?
You look great. Look!
Mason's nose!
Ready! We have long journey ahead.
- Goodbye, Sam!
- Drive carefully!
We'll be back tomorrow night.
Bye, honey.
I'm glad you were born!
This is the car ... Annie
And do you drive a Pontiac GTO?
Baby seats do not go with the other.
No. Just what I had to sell.
What?
Yes, I had to sell.
And ... you no longer have?
A collector
California paid me $ 22,000.
Me fine because
I paid it in cash.
He had paid $ 8500 ages ago.
In general, cars
They are terrible investments.
You take it out of the agency
and you get a used car,
and then on the value decreases.
But, if cared for,
and you're lucky and it's a classic,
the price goes up.
Some people pay hundreds of thousands
dollars for a Ford Shelby Cobra.
What?
Do not you remember?
What do I remember?
Really?
You told me
It would be mine when I turned 16.
What? No, never said that.
I remember. I was in third grade,
and you were carrying me to the house of
Anthony Nagar because it was his birthday.
We took a few laps because
We had arrived early.
You talked about how much
you liked your car.
"It will be of Mason when he turns 16."
First, I do not remember saying that.
Second, never say something. Never.
But you did.
Mason ...
And your sister?
Was I going to forget it?
Come on. Is that fair?
Anthony Nagar, face ... what?
Come on!
You can not ...
You can put a face
burial if you want.
But the issue is simple:it was my car.
I bought it, I took care of him,
I did what I wanted with it.
I'm sorry if you had other hopes.
But when you're older you'll
save up and buy your own car.
And being "cool" as I was.
Or ... you can buy a van.
Your mom lets you look at this?
Yes, she likes it too.
Did you have seen live?
No, but comes to Houston in April.
Are you coming to Houston?
We can get you tickets
and you can stay with us.
- It would be great!
- Yes.
Annie, will you pass me
holds for the gift from Mason?
- Here, honey.
- Need a little explanation.
Open it.
I call it "The disk
black Beatles ".
As it is ...
Best of John, George,
Paul and Ringo after separation.
Thank you.
In short,
gather the band for you.
When you hear a lot of what
they did solo, bored.
But you put next to each other,
and mutually rise.
And then you realize.
Are The Beatles!
I dunno. I think Paul always preferred.
It does not matter. You do not understand the idea.
No favorite Beatle! That is
what I say. The issue is balance.
That was what made hooker
rock band the world's largest!
There are a decade
music that was dispersed.
It has been carefully located,
organized and neat for you ...
by your loving dad.
Very organized and neat
several times by your loving dad.
Sure! Yes! Look at this. Look at this.
The first four issues of volume 2.
From "Band on the Run" to "My Sweet Lord"
a "jealous type" to "Photography".
Hello!
It's the perfect transition!
Paul takes you to a party.
George talks to you about God.
John says
"It is not, about love and pain."
And Ringo says "Can not we enjoy
what we have in the moment "?
- It's a good album. Really.
- Great.
- Hi, Cliff!
- Hello! How are you?
- Good to see you!
- Good to see you.
- Put the icing.
- Wait!
Sam!
Come on.
Are they still asleep?
A wish, a wish!
Gifts! Wait!
Here, honey.
Sam, could you bring
a knife to cut this?
Hope you like it.
I heard you did not have one, so ...
A Bible! Is this your first Bible!
With your name.
Wait, wait.
It's a red letter edition. So it
Jesus says everything is red.
- Thank you.
- Do you like it? Very well.
Honey, happy birthday.
And this is ours.
It is no dream. Lower your expectations.
No, but you need it. It is a ...
You have to have! You need it.
- A lifetime ahead.
- And the shirt is blue.
Dance ... job interviews ...
I'm going to wrinkle.
Mason.
Come here, son.
Desenf鷑dala.
It is a 20 gauge shotgun.
My dad gave me when
I was a little younger than you.
His father had given it.
You're 15 and I want to be yours.
What good.
Hold.
Thank you.
Congratulations, son.
I'll teach you to clean it and shoot it.
I'll show you a little security.
Amart韑lala.
What you want is to align
the front with the rear.
Do you see the little "v"?
- Which would you sign?
- A can of medium.
Is the middle? All right.
Shoot discretion.
Care. Be careful. Very well.
Ready?
You shot a little low.
Expected to rise and then shoot.
It is best when down.
Remember, the second trigger.
Look at that! You hit, right?
- How do you feel?
- All right.
offer to be together forever
A great, wherever you are
want to be easy and informal
But still the man who is
Well, you know we
remain as mysterious
believe all deeply
but always without fear
Scroll to the top, look down from the ledge
And dance barefoot
on the razor's edge
Dreaming big,
get into something dangerous
If I try never will fail
If you ever strip house dice
should not get wet twice in the river
If you love becomes hate too
If you never go home you
Later you'll never
If you eat too much you get fat
If you buy a dog cat angry
Take a deep breath and enjoy the ride
For arrivals and
headings are parallel
They are our first audience.
Mason demanded
rehearse it on the road.
- Admirable
- Lacks work.
A week later - do not know
why Thomas was not at first -
but a week
later, Tom returns ...
and goes with the other disciples.
They say:"The Lord is alive,
! So we have seen! "" I do not believe,
"Until they put my hand into his side,
"And feel the wounds in his hand."
Just then arrives
Jesus stands beside him.
And look at Thomas.
Do you see the shame he felt Thomas?
Thomas looks at him and says:
"Thomas, put your hand in my side."
"Look at my wounds.'s Me"!
And Thomas says:
"My Lord and my God. Thing I think."
And Jesus said, "That's good."
"But blessed
those who believe without seeing. "
It is much easier when
you can see. And feel. And touch.
In our case,
we have not seen in person.
We have not felt in person.
But we have felt
in our spirit; less so.
And I hope you do too.
The lagoon is here.
- What floor!
- Yes.
My dad can take them
to fish next time.
- I'll wait here.
- You want me to stay?
- No, it's fine. - You sure?
- Yes, thank you.
Mason, why are so outdated?
Neither know what you're talking about.
Do not they care back
day 20 for the baptism of Cooper?
- No problem.
- Sam?
Thank you.
It means a lot to Annie and her family.
Were we baptized us?
It was not for nothing
interested in the condition of your soul.
What can we do now,
if you want. You and Cooper together?
縃eads submerged?
Are not you'll become
a man of God, right Dad?
What does that mean?
I hear!
I think the shotgun
will be better at home.
Your mother will not like it.
Watch out, Sam. I'll show you how.
Well, Dad!
Even I can!
- How long have you been here, Mason?
- I'm not sure.
I have. Whole class.
- Did you finish your picture diary?
- Not yet.
And your digital contact sheet?
I lack.
But it did not take long.
"Not yet." "I lack."
The time at
darkroom is extracurricular.
Indeed, nowadays
not even need to be here.
And certainly not if it
you have not completed your tasks.
Here's the issue.
I'm sorry.
I worry, Mason.
- Why?
- I'll tell you.
The images deliveries ...
Cool. You are viewing
things uniquely.
You have so much natural talent.
Thank you.
Yes, but that does not even get
a latte in this world.
I have met many
talented people over the years.
How many have succeeded
as professionals ...
without discipline, commitment,
and a lot of work?
I tell you!
The I can count on two fingers.
Zero!
It will not happen, Mason.
The world is too competitive.
Too many talented people
who are willing to work hard,
and there are many fools who do not have ...
talent, but
they are ready to improve yourself.
Many
are sitting in class now.
You know what they do?
Tasks, which is what
you should be doing,
but you're not.
You are here. Why?
Are you special, Mason?
No. But in regards to the ethics
work, I think I work hard.
Many times I spend
entire weekend taking photos.
Like football, Mason?
- Not much.
- I knew that.
So I just ordered that
you cover the college game today.
It starts at 7 and 30 Arrive early.
I want a full card of photos,
300 images. I want them lowered,
I want them organized
and I want to see early Monday.
Want to know why?
Bue ...
What do you want to be, Mason?
What do you do?
I want to take pictures.
Making art.
Any moron
You can take pictures, Mason.
Art is something else.
What can you contribute
no one else can?
It's what I'm trying to figure out.
Try harder.
Maybe in 20 years
Mr. Turlington call the old ...
and you tell him "thank you, sir" ...
for that big talk in the dark room.
Go back to class and get to work.
You walk a little weird.
Fuck you.
I say. They were in a long time.
Hope you have paid dinner.
Mason! To eat, honey!
Samantha! Still not uploaded
photos with descriptions?
Come on. The auction ends on Sunday.
You have to publish.
What do we do?
It looks like a junk shop.
- I thought you had a good job.
- What I have.
But the house has many expenses.
Everyone has to contribute.
Your brother took the pictures ...
You have to collaborate.
Who buys this shit?
Sam, careful what you say.
Do not disrespect your mother.
Want to
roof over your head, right?
And electricity to charge your cell phone?
Next year I will not be.
I should have fun in the last year.
That beautiful nails.
The painted girl in school.
- Will you let it?
- Thru the enamel, I think.
Last summer
the earings now nails ...
Do not have a portfolio combining?
Many do it to look "cool".
When I was in
high ... and working,
be responsible,
to buy a car,
was "cool".
Mason, please go get the water.
Hey. Enough said Turlington
Art and take pictures of the game.
So point your lens there.
- God.
- And we're off.
They sent us tickets to the party.
We're coming after the game.
Party photos.
First! What's up? What's up?
- Hello, Mason.
- How you doing?
All right. How long have you been here long?
- I dunno. A while.
- A while?
I feel like there's so much ...
I could be doing and
I want to be doing but do not.
Why not?
I think it is fear ...
what people will think.
- You know, trials.
- Yes.
It's easy to say, "No I
care what other people think "
- But everyone cares.
- That's right.
In the background.
I get angry with many people
with whom I am in touch ...
because I control
or whatever, but ...
they do not even realize they do.
And in this world
where no one plays perfect ...
What is different? What changes?
Everything. I just want
do whatever you want.
That makes me feel alive.
Instead of giving me
the appearance of normality.
Whatever it is.
I do not think much.
You're a little weird, you know?
Is it a compliment?
I dunno. Want to be weird?
I do not want to scare ...
children in the park or something.
I like talking to you.
I do not usually try to vocalize
my thoughts, feelings, or anything.
Never sounds good.
Words are ... stupid.
And why you try me?
I dunno. I think because I feel comfortable.
I'm glad.
Hi, Jim. Sorry I'm late.
What time you had to get there?
I dunno. A while ago.
A guy while ...
Thirty minutes? An hour?
No one knew where you were
until your sister said.
She arrived earlier.
I'm sorry.
I hear that a lot lately.
But ... you do not really care.
You come and go at your leisure.
You do not care if your
mother is concerned,
or what time you should arrive.
Is that the story?
- I do not know what to say.
- Stop babbling!
Speak up!
Do not understand a
word. Sounds like "mhmmm" ...
And I'm asking questions and you just ...
Can it be a day without
everyone is fucking with me?
Would I fuck?
It's my home.
If you want to live in my house, comes
when you said you'd be.
You know, Jim? You're not my dad.
I know I'm not your dad.
You know how I know?
Because I'm here.
I'm the one who has a job, pays
bills, take care of you, your mom ...
your sister ... Huh? Eh?
That's me!
CORRECTIONS
- Good day.
Who of you
used the downstairs bathroom last night?
I dunno. It was not me.
The high, what's his name?
- Phillip?
- Yes, Phillip.
Phillip 縭ead?
Sign that says:
"Do not use this bathroom is broken."
Is it so difficult?
I dunno. I'm sorry.
I think it will make the house for sale.
Why?
It's very big for us.
Soon you're going to college.
It is very expensive. Basta.
What you bought?
Because I love taking
bad decisions in my life.
And have you on the edge of poverty.
I spent half
of my life buying crap ...
and now I will go the other
quit醤domelas half off.
Yeah? Like what?
I shook off two spouses.
Now it's up to the
mortgage, maintenance,
Trinkets, insurance ...
owners, property taxes,
pipes ..
Do you know? Now
Mommy will be more monk.
Simple. Celibate.
That sucks, Mom.
Good. Then I will be a
poor bitch with a big house.
Does it sound better?
Mason, please
do not leave me the dirty plate.
I wash dishes all day.
All right! You're a professional. You can
wash one or two others for your poor mother.
- OK.
- Thank you.
Want one?
Nor touched. I watched all the time.
To who do you observe degenerate.
It's like dating.
Health!
A romantic evening.
But I will not kiss.
Although I suck you.
Mason! There is emergency in the lounge.
I do it as quickly as possible.
I must have confused then.
Because recently I saw chatting with April.
We must renew salads.
6 A table, two tables
4 I can not use,
because they are dirty.
Enrique did not come. I do what I can.
Well, we're in trouble.
What do you tell clients?
"Sorry about the dirty dishes,
but Mason does what he can. "
"That's what he told me."
"After flirting with April
and eat shrimp that had been ".
I know that today is difficult.
But I want to tell you something.
I have scheduled you
Waiters this summer.
It's a lot more responsibility.
And more money.
What do you think?
All right.
I know you can with the money, but
you can handle the responsibility?
I think so. Because I believe in you.
I need you in the lounge.
Leave the dishes and hurry.
Come on. Do not disappoint me!
Does it work well?
Is the alternator does not give more trouble?
All right. Ready for the trip.
Are you going to see your sister in Austin?
Yeah, he said I could stay
in his uni dorm.
I think your partner is
travel, so no problem.
Already you applied for UT?
Would you have sent the form?
Not yet, but Sheena
is practically accepted.
If that's where you want to go ...
You should postularte
for early acceptance.
Let them know you're
a man who knows what he wants.
Some firmness
achieved much in this life.
- No?
- Yes.
And work? How's it going?
All right. Today was
a bad day. He missed a guy.
But no doubt it gives
another perspective on life.
People are pig!
When they ask you,
say "A Mason is doing very well."
"You have a job. Cleans everything."
Say hello to Annie and Cooper.
Say hello to your big brother.
"Hello, brother."
Hi Annie. Hello, friend.
Say goodbye.
See you.
Be careful when driving.
Do not send text messages or anything.
You Obi Wan.
Focused and patient ... is not it?
Three cars Watch
in front and two behind.
It takes two bad
leads to an accident.
Tell your sister that
grab your phone and call me.
- Well, my friend. Have a good time.
- Goodbye, Dad.
Take this to your sister.
Put it on the truck.
- And where Sheena sleep?
- With her friend Emily.
- Does Emily?
- Yes!
It is in the third year.
He has his own apartment.
This is for emergencies.
Do not spend it, I want it back.
Thank you.
Did you do your homework?
Almost everything, but I'll finish tomorrow.
The junior year is very
important for uni. Do not blow it.
I know, I know.
That's what we're going to UT.
Do not you want to go? "Sheena, what
a trip with Mom "? Promissory gasoline.
I'm kidding. I have work.
- Call me when you get there.
- I will do it.
Have fun!
Sounds to me like a vision
all very simplistic.
Not at all. Finally I got it.
When they realized
it would be too expensive ...
build cyborgs and robots,
or whether the costs were
soaring, they decided that humans ...
self transformed into robots.
- That's what's happening.
- Right now?
Why not? There are billions of
ours out there, doing nothing.
We have cost.
And until we self-maintenance,
and we reproduce constantly.
And as we can see, we're ...
biologically programmed
to become cyborgs.
- As?
- Seriously.
I read an article the other day saying ...
when we heard the sound
the inbox
received an injection
dopamine in our brains.
As if we rewarded chemically
for letting it get brainwashed.
Is it not evil? We're screwed!
You think to delete your
Facebook page will change anything?
I remember when it did Traver
last year. And everyone laughed at him.
You laughed more than anyone.
I keep laughing at Traver.
Your need for attention was pathetic.
Or to be different, or something.
And it ended with that silly story
about it in the school newspaper.
And I had to make a great
ad when he returned the following month.
But I do not care.
I want to try to live
my life without a screen.
I want a real interaction.
A real person.
No profile posted online.
Apology. What were you saying?
It's okay.
I know you're joking, but ...
there is some truth. You
state with your phone the entire trip.
What do you do actually?
If you do not care what they do
friends on Saturday afternoon,
you're not immersed
my deep grievances,
and it seems that all
They are in a place in between.
Without experiencing anything seriously.
It is not an experience.
It's just information.
Mira. For example:
I got the address
club where we meet.
Therefore we do not lose
the streets of Austin later.
Thank you very much, Facebook.
And I sent a text to my mom.
Revolutionary!
You have not seen you for 55 minutes.
God! The most important ...
I was told that
we have a miniature pig.
You're right. This is ...
It is a very cute pig.
Our lives can continue.
I want one.
Nice shot.
Show him one
identification and will pass.
Room 206, right?
- But do not spend the night there.
- All right. Have fun.
Thank you.
How long you go out together?
About three months.
We met at a party and all good.
- It seems quiet.
- Yes, it is.
- It also goes to the University of Texas?
- Yes.
What are you studying?
History and Italian ...
as a secondary subject.
Want to teach?
I dunno. I think he is still thinking.
He already decided. He's smart.
And where you live when you come here?
I'm not sure.
We will look at some apartments ...
morning.
My parents assume that
I live in a college dorm.
But I will pay the uni, so ...
not so important.
You do not have to listen to what
tell your parents after 18.
Especially if you do not help financially.
That's what I thought.
The bedrooms are not bad.
Especially if they are mixed.
I had never been
surrounded by so many handsome guys.
The uni is fun!
- I'm excited.
- It's good, yes.
The day I was born I started to age
nobody told me that life
I could be so lonely and cruel
He had gray hair at 23
this life
bad luck will end with me
The old black crow
grooves has left me in the face
and on the go
I'm in the same place
The hard life will end with me
The latest death during construction
Hoover dam was his son,
Patrick Tierney,
who died on December 20, 1935.
Just thirteen years later.
Do you see the girls in the sisterhood?
I already decided. If you delete your
Facebook page, I will launch me.
Yes, in a few years
that will be you ... and that will be me.
A star map. A map
of heavenly bodies as accurate ...
that could plot the position of the
North Star 14,000 years later ...
and future generations ...
I wonder what it does.
Do not come to eat.
It is. He is a professor at UT.
And with the post insured.
Look at all these people.
Why are you here at three in the morning?
What we do
at three in the morning?
You know why we're here?
The cheese! We have a purpose.
Right.
In the next summer,
so will our lives.
Staying up all night. View shows.
What we want.
Do you also classes?
- Every so.
- Sounds good.
- Until inspiration strikes.
- Only at the time.
- Anything else?
- More cheese?
- God ...
- What?
Is not it a bit overwhelming?
The university ...
I like the idea
living away from home, and ...
acquire knowledge
and improve my photos, but it is ...
I do not think it is
transformative.
Do not think it's as transformative.
It's just the next step.
It's like a preset space
you already have your name and number.
Not think that's the key to my future.
Look at my mom.
He graduated and got a job.
- Pays the bills ...
- I like your mom.
Me too, but I mean ...
In the background,
she is as confused as me.
Thank you.
Hello?
Hi! Oh ...
Not Sam told you
we ... we'd be here?
No.
Sorry, uh ...
We said you'd be ...
out the weekend.
I was. And I just got back.
Are you her ... brother?
Yes, I am ... I'm a Mason.
She is Sheena.
What good.
All right. I will leave my
things and I'm going to eat something ...
- And I'll be back in a while.
- We have to go soon ...
so ...
- All right. Nice to meet you.
- Same here.
Sorry!
It was so uncomfortable!
Mason! Winner of the silver medal.
- Congratulations!
- Thank you.
- I found out about the scholarship.
- Yes all helps..
When you go to there?
In the summer, I think.
And I will work a little earlier.
I want to save some money.
Before you have to make do.
That's the idea.
How do you feel?
Excited.
Half excited, half terrified.
- This voluptuous panic.
- That's right.
It will be good. It will be great for you.
To me I like the uni
much more than high school.
Find your own
people in the uni, you know?
That's right.
You'll be fine. Have a good
heart. Listen to your heart.
- Thank you.
- Good luck. Do not forget to floss.
- YOU SEE THE THREE. WHAT?
- I CAN NOT, SEE YOU TOMORROW.
I do not understand why
you act like a child.
Not so. Thou became a
something big to tell everyone.
I did not tell anyone.
And how do you know Cynthy
you go to the party with a loser,
despite not seeing him?
- He's my best friend.
- Your best friend has a big mouth.
Talk it over with her, then.
Why did not you tell
it was Robert Tosh?
You can keep talking,
while including truth
which is not
would have this conversation ...
if your boyfriend was not uni
outside this weekend.
You had already bought the tickets.
Does not matter.
I just wanted to be friendly.
It is a humiliation. I can not do it.
Mr. "I do not care
what anyone thinks of me. "
Fuck that. I care what
I think for me, it's no big deal.
The King of the Pity Party.
Okay, we will not.
Fantastic.
What we are ...
We knew this was coming.
I'm the one who did something about it.
- Yes, you fucked a guy from uni.
- Fuck you!
- I do not regret anything.
- Of course not.
It's a relief to be with someone
who is not depressed all the time.
The world is not so horrible.
Not everything is a big conspiracy.
I'm glad you could think so.
Sure dating an athlete
helps you ... clear your mind.
It's not an athlete.
It is only on the lacrosse team.
We will be in universities
different next year.
It is not such a serious relationship.
Great! Now I feel much better.
- I want to have fun.
- A well he passes.
Madura, Mason.
I have not been alone.
Who?
What do you care?
- Who?
- Who cares?
You brought it up.
It makes no sense.
Now you're playing the fool.
Fuck! I would rather
to cut my balls ...
rather than having to
endure something like that again.
- Well, not never touch us.
- Thank God.
- Give me.
- All for you. Drink it all.
Do you go out with me tonight?
There are very interesting things there.
I'm going to see a show
with my father in Austin.
Some friends playing.
Well, have fun.
Fuck! There are both cars.
I do not want to enter.
Man, you both have fun.
Your family loves you.
That passes very well.
- You're coming with me.
- No, no, hell, no. - Yes!
My mom loves you. You have to say hello.
Want offend?
Well come on!
One second. Just a second, really.
- You're in enemy territory.
- We already know.
Look who's here!
Wait, wait. We will take photos.
Got a camera?
Congratulations, baby.
I do not know you, but I congratulate you.
Very well. Look here.
- Smile!
- Ready!
That was good.
Sam, where are you? Samantha!
And Mason father?
I am generous, come here.
Beautiful!
They'll send the email.
Do not start. Do not start.
It seems incredible that have been
so far. I was grateful.
We would not have missed for anything
world. I'm proud of you.
Congratulations!
I regret that Lee could not come.
It's graduation trip.
- Send greetings.
- I will do it.
Abby, I did not recognize.
How old are you now?
- Thirteen.
- Unbelievable.
A fill!
- Will you?
- Yes, of course.
I brought you something.
What is it?
It is a savings bond. It has its value.
It is better than money,
did you spend it.
- Go, is that your mom?
- Yes, she is.
Rule three seconds.
Put it on the plate.
I want to make a toast to Mason!
Mason, I know not
wanted a party tonight, but ...
we do.
Just finish
secondary once in life!
And I want festejarte,
and celebrate the next stage ...
You will learn both the
university. You'll laugh so much.
Have teachers who inspire you.
You will learn more of your art.
I love you. I'm proud of you.
- By Mason.
- By Mason!
Touches you, brother.
Sure, uh ... Well ...
Mason, a toast
by ... future. For your future.
It has been difficult
this ... end of school year.
Wondering what college you choose.
Mason said he wanted ...
be as far from home as possible,
while maintaining the agreement
to stay in the state.
What I appreciate that.
It is a wise man
and will have a great future.
To your health, friend.
Son Mason!
Just graduated, 18 and hetero!
I ignore it.
My brother needs
learn to control.
I do not know you both
as the others here.
But since you
I met've grown a lot.
And I'm proud of you.
If photography is not working,
always have a job - without the hoop.
Maybe you can locate
in the receiving part. To your health!
Sam, a word!
Come on, Sam.
Come on, baby!
Good luck!
- So you broke up with your girlfriend?
- Yes, recently.
- What was his name?
- Sheena.
Sheena. Did you go to college?
No. No ... stay ...
on this side of Texas.
Do you need a ride to uni?
I wanted to say hello
before they left.
Are known, do not you, Annie?
- Yes, Sam ... graduation.
- Right.
And where is the little one?
He stayed at home.
He was very upset at Sam.
I'd love to see it!
We expect a
special weekend, and ...
I'm so glad that you met.
You met him at a good time, I think.
I think so.
- Good to see you.
- Me too.
- I'm proud of your son.
- We all are.
She's a witch!
You remember going to the uni, you know?
And if you look
something to me or your father,
you go down a few women.
You will pistoning followed.
You will exercise followed.
Think about it. There are many flowers in this bouquet.
But do me a favor.
This summer you will
in a vulnerable position.
Protect yourself during sex separation.
And he knows what I'm talking about.
Look what happened to him. Voila!
Steven ...
Health.
- It's not that simple.
- Four more years!
- Recycle?
- There's a bag there.
Am I your only ex husband at the party?
Yes.
But I am not your only wife here.
Can you believe that both
finished school?
No.
I can not.
You've done a great job with both.
Thanks for saying that.
I never thought I'd hear you say that.
It's the truth. Thank you.
- And you do it again.
- I know, I know.
Missing 15 years
that has the ... empty nest.
I like to help.
To help with this.
It is very good that you have done.
I just wanted to give you a little ... ...
- If I may help.
- Sure, sure.
I have no cash.
It's in the portfolio of Annie. Be right back.
Tough. The guy is a player
lacrosse uni. What can you do?
She neither likes sports.
- A beer?
- No thanks.
- You can drink a.
All has happened to us
the same in one way or another.
It's not the same.
You never knew well.
I know it's not the same.
I do not know what I did wrong.
Hi, Jimmy! Hello.
Hello, Mason.
We are hunting in the
green room, is there problem?
All ten points.
Is that MJ?
Incredible.
We decided to come early to see you.
Term and will be with you for a while.
I guarantee that you did nothing wrong.
Those Loves
Secondary never work.
All are
are changing so fast, you know?
The odds that two young
remain on the same wavelength are ...
- Yes, but ...
- I also guarantee ...
every day of your life
you spend crying over a silly girl ...
It is a waste of time.
But it was not a silly girl.
It is a serious person.
I really thought ...
What?
I dunno.
The truth is that
Women are never satisfied.
They are always
redeem looking model.
Sorry, but that
is what happened to you, great friend.
What does that mean?
It means that you give not
control of your self-esteem Sheila.
Sheena.
It means that you are responsible for
yourself. Not your girlfriend, your mom, or me.
You. And if you really
you take care of yourself ...
you be surprised how many girls
Sheena as knocking at your door.
Great.
You have to find a way
to separate you from the pack.
You excel at something, you know?
And there you can choose what you want
herd when you advanced ...
start to sniff.
So I should devote myself to lacrosse.
Right.
O ... form a rock band.
It worked for me long ago
And it still functions Jimmy.
O still taking pictures.
She hated the pictures I took him.
I'm sick of it.
I only saw a couple
times and, yes, it was cute.
But in truth,
I always thought that was a bit ...
a bit boring for you.
They were not on the same wavelength.
You know what occurred to me?
He was at a lower level.
I was not surprised that
are interested in lacrosse baby.
Basically, it all depends
of time on these things.
Look at your mom and me.
I think I've become ...
type boring and neutered
she wanted 15-20 years ago.
I'm not saying he was wrong to be angry.
I'm just saying it could
have been a little more patient.
A little more forgiving.
I would have saved
the parade of drunken morons.
What's the point?
What?
I dunno. This. Everything.
Everything?
What's the point?
What the fuck do I know?
Neither one knows why. All ...
improvise, you know?
The good thing is that you feel things.
And you have to hold on to that.
You grow up and do not feel much.
The skin becomes hard.
The sense you get is the photos.
They sent photos
statewide and you won.
I won silver.
Along with others.
What I'm saying is that I believe in you, Mason.
I think you're special. And if you
girl can not see, fuck.
This issue is dedicated
a young present.
I met him when I was a kid.
Now finished school
secondary and makes me feel old.
You graduate, Mason.
Thank you.
The record straight.
There will be four categories.
A:Anything
childhood who want to carry.
Two:Things to shoot.
Three:Things to donate.
Four:What we want to try to
sell at the show this weekend.
What is not sold will be donated.
Does the apartment does not have
an attic, storage or something?
No. You do not understand.
We will not take crap
old my little apartment.
Another move, can not believe it.
I move. You moved in like two years ago.
Have an apartment in Austin.
Mason moves in the fall.
I finished!
It will be great. I will have many options.
Me I can take a sabbatical.
I can devote myself to writing.
Get to publish me.
What about Christmas?
What will we do?
I will not share a room with him.
One of you will sleep on the couch.
We will use the inflatable mattress.
And how to wash my clothes?
I'm giving a
nudge to leave the nest.
And perhaps falling magically
find some coins ...
to wash clothes
in your own apartment.
But please! You are ... adults.
They have to take responsibility.
What do they want?
I the veggie burger.
Nothing for me. I'm not hungry.
What's wrong?
I feel bad.
What do you have? Does the head? Do you have a fever?
You are pregnant.
In fact, I drank too much last night.
- There were driving, right?
- No, no.
Carrie is back too.
The spent together.
- A drink with Jack Daniel's that down ...
- No, no.
No excuse.
Like you can fill boxes. People
you want to move as fast as possible.
Hello.
Ernesto'm Larrio.
She did not remember me, but ...
I am the pipe a few years ago.
Right.
Believe it or not, it changed my life.
I said I was
intelligent and had to go to uni.
And I took his advice.
First with English classes.
A year later I went to college
communal and managed a tertiary degree.
Now I'm in uni
state after licensure.
And I am one of the managers here.
Hottie!
Glad to see it and to have
the opportunity to thank them.
It was a big deal for me.
Lunch is on me.
- It's the least I can do.
- Thank you.
Let her case. It's a smart woman.
Thank you.
Is not that crazy?
A computer knows who you are ...
twenty questions on a form.
There seems to be only
Eight types of people worldwide.
There are subsets
as males and females, but ...
apparently we are not
as unique as we think.
Have you talked to him?
No, but we exchanged messages.
It looks nice. Literature Study ...
and anthropology, and loves
Bright Eyes, which is a good thing.
And he told me that ...
the system to assign peers
bedroom gives a little scary.
The satisfaction rate of the Nerds
with peers used to be 60%.
And now it is 100%.
Only by the computer.
It will be a good companion, then.
But we conclude that ...
soon will not need a questionnaire.
The NSA will scan
your digital ghost and ...
they will tell you who your partner,
based on everything
ever said, wrote or you clicked.
You put it in again?
I do not want.
Come on! It's the first picture you get.
Precisely why I leave, right?
- What's up?
- Nothing!
Mom, what's wrong?
Nothing!
Mom ...
It's the worst day of my life!
What are you talking about?
I knew this day would come.
I could not imagine
you'd be so happy to go!
Not that I'm so happy.
What did you expect?
You know what I'm thinking?
That my life is just like that!
These milestones of life.
Getting married, having children, divorce.
That time when
thought you were dyslexic.
When I taught you to ride a bike!
Getting divorced ... again!
Getting my masters.
Finally getting the job you wanted.
Send to Samantha to uni.
Sending you to college!
You know what follows, eh?
My fucking funeral!
Go away and leave my photo!
Have not you're getting ahead forty years?
I just thought that ... would be more.
Let go
not wanna be your hero
do not want to be a great man
just want to fight with all
Your farce
do not want to be part of your parade
Everyone deserves a chance to
Walking with everyone else
While I keep
A work to be with my girl
And maybe buy new strings
out with her on weekends
And we can whisper things
Secrets of our American dreams
The baby needs protection
But I'm a child like everyone else
Well let me go
not wanna be your hero
do not want to be a great man
just want to fight like everyone else
You must be Mason.
Dalton, right?
How nice to finally meet you.
Does this side is good for you?
- Yes.
- I arrived in the morning and threw everything there.
All right. Do not worry.
Need help with something? Suitcases ?
I can only box
and is quite light, but ...
- I thank you.
- You're welcome.
Will you go to the orientation?
縊rientation Meeting?
Fuck that! I will not go.
And neither, for that matter.
We have better things to do.
- Ready?
- Yeah Hey ... Barb.
my mate
fourth Mason. Mason, Barb.
- Are you coming with us?
- Where are they going?
- A day trip.
- Yes, come with us.
If we leave now we will see
sunset in Big Bend. Do you know?
Child.
More reason to come now.
That's why we're here.
Mason, she is Nicole,
Barb companion.
- What about?
- Hi.
- Mason, Nicole.
- So? Are you coming?
Sure.
Here, this ends.
The perfect time. He pasted
when we get to the mountains.
Hottie! Underway.
Would you allow the main subject?
Well, it's not so important here ...
so I train
out of college, but ...
course all the basics here
as dance history and stuff.
What do you teach?
Oops! Good ...
Ballet, tap dancing
American, jazz, hip hop ...
- Which do you prefer?
- The stomping.
You can invent ...
your own sounds and ...
no rules. There is freedom to create.
- That's good.
- Yes.
So I like to teach it, then ...
It is so beautiful to me and is
turning in this generation.
Help give back to the kids.
It is very rewarding.
- How old are they?
- Sixteen
Not afraid
and they are not shy at all.
Not yet arrived
at age a sense of embarrassment.
No. I will come to you.
Dalton do crazy things sometimes.
Looks good people.
Yes. Yes, both are.
How do you feel?
All right.
Very well, in fact.
Glad you have joined the group.
Me too.
The moment is having
a wonderful orgasm!
It is as if all time had
deployed so that we are here ...
and look and shout:Fuck, yeah!
Did you see how people
always says "seize the moment"?
I tend to think that is backwards.
The moment captures us.
Yes.
Yes, of course, is ... is constant.
The time is ...
It's like always
out now, you know?
Yes.
(subtitle from http://shooter.cn by SPlayer2501
Subtitle:I scalisto
(subtitle from http://shooter.cn by SPlayer